{"classes":["ORG","PERSON"],"annotations":[["Tesla Motors was founded as an electric carmaker by engineers Martin Eberhard and Marc Tarpenning in 2003. \r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"],[62,77,"PERSON"],[82,97,"PERSON"]]}],["Elon Musk, co-founder of Paypal, led the initial rounds of investing for Tesla before taking over as CEO. In 2008, \r",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[25,31,"ORG"]]}],["Tesla released its first electric car, the Roadster.\r",{"entities":[]}],["Meta builds technologies that help people connect, find communities, and grow businesses. \r",{"entities":[[0,4,"ORG"]]}],["When Facebook launched in 2004, it changed the way people connect. \r",{"entities":[[5,13,"ORG"]]}],["Apps like Messenger, Instagram and WhatsApp further empowered billions around the world. \r",{"entities":[]}],["Now, Meta is moving beyond 2D screens toward immersive experiences like augmented and \r",{"entities":[[5,9,"ORG"]]}],["virtual reality to help build the next evolution in social technology.\r",{"entities":[]}],["Flipkart was founded in October 2007 by Sachin Bansal and Binny Bansal, alumni of the IIT, \r",{"entities":[[0,8,"ORG"],[40,53,"PERSON"],[58,70,"PERSON"],[86,89,"ORG"]]}],["Delhi and former Amazon employees. \r",{"entities":[[17,23,"ORG"]]}],["The company initially focused on online book sales with country-wide shipping. \r",{"entities":[]}],["Flipkart slowly grew in prominence and was receiving 100 orders per day by 2008.\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"ORG"]]}],["This is when Mukesh Ambani's Reliance Limited started working on establishing a base \r",{"entities":[[13,26,"PERSON"],[29,45,"ORG"]]}],["for a high-speed optical fiber 4G network which is much more capable than 4G. \r",{"entities":[]}],["The company was named Reliance Jio Infocom Ltd popularly known as Jio today. \r",{"entities":[[22,46,"ORG"]]}],["Jio was the first network to provide 4G LTE services and VoLTE services\r",{"entities":[[0,3,"ORG"]]}],["",{"entities":[]}]]}